

Paweł Sawczuk



ISHIDA530@GMAIL.COM



ABOUT ME

I'm 27 years old. After graduating from the technical school I left the economics field on the IT profile abroad for profit. After almost 5 years with my family decided to return to homeland. I decided to get a job as a junior front end programmer

LANGUAGES

- Intermediate English
- Native Polish

COURSES AND TRAINING

- 2020 Bootcamp Front-End by Akademia Kodu-150hours
- 2020 MTA: HTML5 Application Development Fundamentals - 30hours
- 2020 Multiple courses for front-end developer: Base HTML/CSS-38hours Advenced HTML/CSS- 38.5hours Javascript -37 hours
- 2020 Basic skills from WordPress 30hours
- 2020 ECDL BASE certificat 80hours
- 2020 Interpersonal Skills Training
- 2020 Qualified First Aid (RECERTIFICATION)
- 2019 Driver course forklift operator all types
- 2014 Driving License course, category B
- 2013 Motorboat helmsman

EXPERIENCE

Junior front-end developer · XYBRYZT· 12.02.2021 (currently)

(Wodzislaw Slaski - Poland)

Building websites and online stores on the Wordpress platform

Junior front-end developer · NoMonday · 3.11.2020 -3.02.2021 (intership)

(Rybnik - Poland)

- manual testing
- HTML templates based on Adobe XD project
- website optimization
- layout of mailings from the use of MJML
- working with WordPress templates
- creating a SPA using Webpack, Bootstrap

Forklift driver • HENKEL POLSKA • 7.2020 -30.09.2020

(Racibórz - Poland)

Working in the warehouse, delivering production

SELLER / WAREHOUSE • WHOLESALE "OPIUM" FLOWERS • 2.2020 - 3.2020

(Racibórz - Poland)

Warehouse work, transport of goods to the customer 3.5t bus / customer service

ORDERPICKER • JUMBO • 5.2017 - 3.2019

(Woerden - Netherlands)

Collecting orders in warehouses and distribution of goods with a forklift

ORDERPICKER • DIRK • 3.2017 - 5.2017

(Bleiswijk - Netherlands)

Collecting orders in warehouses and distribution of goods with a forklift



TECHNOLOGY

- HTML/CSS
- Preprocessor SASS/SCSS
- JavaScript/jQuery
- Bootstrap/Materialize
- GIT/Gitflow

STRENGTHS

- √ Diligence
- √ Willingness to develop
- √ Dynamics in action
- √ Honesty
- √ Openness
- √ Team work

REFERENCE

OTTO Work Force B.V.

Keizersveld 51
5803 AP Venray
Postbus 5145
5800 GC Venray
T +31 (0)478 529999
F +31 (0)478 529900
info@OTTOworkforce.eu
www.OTTOworkforce.eu

EDUCATION

TEAM OF ECONOMIC SCHOOLS M. COPERNICUS NUMBER. 7, IN OLSZTYN

Profile: IT specialist From 2010 to 2014

INTERESTS

In my spare time, I learn and develop my skills in creating websites. I like to travel and collect experience from each place I go to. Sport is very important, always played sports.



